What's the point of
having the best results of finalist season?
We still didn't even go to the finals
because of someone...
And finally gave
the trophy to the opponent.
Who actually led to
Ming's severe hand injury?
Not all mistakes
can be covered by time.
Lu Yue will definitely
not be the starting player.
Anyway, this must have been
done by someone among us.
I posted the video.
Chubby?
Why did you have the fight?
Why did you get Ming involved in?
Why did you drag the whole team down?
You're just a coward
who runs away all the time!
What did you say?!
I'll say it as many times as I please!
You are a coward!
Chubby, stop it!
Shut up! I dare you to say it again!
You're just a coward.
- That's enough, Chubby.
- Let's go.
Let's go. Go out and calm down.
Chubby, you made a mistake.
Lu Yue didn't fight
with others for no reason.
Obviously, it was Lu Yue's fault.
Why are you guys trying to
cover for him all the time?
The truth is often more than meets the eye.
Do you want to hear about it?
What exactly happened a year ago?
=Falling into Your Smile=
=Episode 08=
Hey, Yao, I know that...
Don't hang up, Yao!
Go watch Ai Jia's live streaming.
He's trying to help Lu Yue clarify online.
It's a coincidence.
I was having a diarrhea
in the toilet at the time.
(The JK people were indeed distasteful.)
(It takes two to make a quarrel.)
You have no idea
(Lu Yue deserves to be banned for a year.)
what a pain in the ass the JK people were.
(What kind of rubbish is ZGDX?)
(Look at their cocky faces.)
They're too arrogant.
That's right.
Especially Lu Yue.
His brother didn't show up
at tonight's cocktail party, either.
And he dared to mess around.
(Didn't even show some respect to our A.)
(A spent the money,)
so much money
just for a promotion before the game.
(Now guess what?)
(It went live)
and we ended with a 2:0.)
Didn't we have a deal?
It's a performance game,
and just make it 2:1 and call it a game.
Okay, forget about the score,
but what's up with their cocky attitude?
They're really asking for a beating.
Also,
if A were in a better state today,
they'd have had no chance at winning.
That's right.
(So what if they can get to the finals?)
(They're too arrogant.)
(I know.)
They want to get in the national finals?
Stop dreaming.
No respect for me,
then I'll show them
what it means to have no mercy.
Hello?
(Get over here in a while.)
(Yep.)
Bring more people
and rip the hands
off of those little bastards
of ZGDX.
By the way,
be careful when you do it.
Don't hurt the second son of the Lu family.
Wait, A,
(why isn't Lu Yue included?)
(He's from the Lu Family.)
(It'll cause a lot of trouble.)
This fight
was purely initiated by A.
He said himself that
he'd find people
to break the hands of
those professional players.
Who are those professional players?
The ZGDX players.
Bros.
They were looking for people
to break the hands of ZGDX players,
and they weren't joking.
They actually made the phone call.
(If it were you,)
(wouldn't you step up)
(in a situation like this?)
(If the people they asked for
really came over,)
(then it'd have been too late.)
(So, this is how the whole thing happened.)
(I only tell you the truth,)
(and I don't judge.)
Think about it.
Bye-bye.
Lu Yue.
Since we're all in the same team,
you shouldn't have hidden the fact
that you fought to protect us to begin with.
They were right about one thing.
Your hand got injured
because of my fight.
Lu Yue.
All right.
Now that everything's clear,
nobody should hold on to the past.
But I'm still partly responsible
for your hand injury.
So even if I confess it,
it wouldn't change anything.
Chubby is right.
I did drag you down,
and the team as well.
Anyway,
it's true that Lu Yue was too impulsive.
But it's not
entirely
Lu Yue's fault.
After all,
A from JK was too mean.
Yeah, if it were me,
who heard that someone
was going to beat up my bros,
I'd get into the fight as well.
Am I right?
So we can't blame everything
on Lu Yue.
You guys shouldn't think this way.
You should go to the police instead.
That's right.
Sue him and get him to beg for forgiveness.
Now that we all know the truth,
K,
Chubby,
are you guys
fine now?
Lu Yue.
I am sorry.
It's my bad.
I was wrong about you.
It's okay.
Cheng,
I think we should
make the truth public first.
It might not change
the public opinion completely,
but at least we should let people know
that we didn't start the fight.
I'll call the PR department
to see how it should proceed.
Lu Yue,
sorry.
I don't feel wronged.
I did make
the worst decision.
Lu Yue,
when you encounter something like this,
you should call me as soon as possible.
If I were there,
Ming's hand would have been fine.
If you had called me,
I could've…
called the police,
right?
Okay, forget it.
(Cheng is here! Cheng is here!)
(I finally get to see people
from ZGDX live streaming.)
(Curiosity kills me.)
(Can Cheng explain the fight?)
(Why did Lu Yue start the fight?)
It was indeed Lu Yue
who made the first move.
As for why,
you can go watch Ai Jia's live streaming.
(Ming's hand got injured,
and you guys quit the final.)
(That's why you fought, right?)
(3-second silence tribute for Ming.)
Ming's hand got injured due to an accident.
Truly,
it's related to this,
but Ming had injured his hand before as well.
This is common among professional players.
A tendon tear.
It's normal for those
who play in a core position.
(No matter what, Lu Yue was too impulsive.)
(Cheng,)
(if it were you,)
(what would you have done?)
I won't beat them up.
But I will let those
who bully my teammates know
what it means to regret.
(ZGDX contract renewal)
Look.
This is my contract renewal with the club.
Why don't you take your time
to practice more
shikigamis instead of showing off?
Is it time to give me a regular spot, right?
I can't always fight with this fool
for the computer all day,
right? Ming.
That should tell you
who's the more crucial one.
I'm talking about
adding a computer desk for you.
Chubby has been busy
in the kitchen since this morning.
I think it's going to be something big.
What's he doing?
I'm guessing
he's trying to make up to everyone
by making a dinner.
Chubby,
I didn't know you were good at this.
I've been in the team for so long,
but this is the first time I've seen this.
What do you want? I'll get it for you.
No, I'm fine.
You guys just take your seats.
Rui,
I heard that Chubby was fined
three months of his salary this time.
Really?
This means anytime he might ask me
to lend him some money
within these three months.
Can I choose not to eat
this miserable meal?
I won't eat it either.
Stop the sarcasm,
or else both of you will be fined.
OK, I'll eat it.
I deserve it.
I deserve all of it.
Chubby,
even though you got fined,
shouldn't you at least
get another pound of meat
to treat us?
There's nothing here.
Yeah, not even
a single piece of meat in there.
Hand it to me if you guys
don't want to eat it.
No, no.
I'll eat it.
Let me dig deeper.
Do you want mine?
Do you have meat?
A little.
What are you doing?
What the... Chubby.
I thought the act of
hiding meat in the bowl
for your favorite child
has been long gone since my mother's time.
I…
See,
he's mad now.
Lu Yue, I was wrong.
I shouldn't have led the negative
public opinion against you
before seeing the whole picture.
I'm sorry.
Sooner or later,
this door will collapse because of Chubby.
Great.
Now get serious.
So everyone's okay with Lu Yue
returning to the team this time, right?
Yes.
Then I'll submit the roster
for the new season tomorrow.
Wait, what?
What do you mean by everyone?
Why is everyone okay with it?
How about me?
I'm not okay with that.
All new members
must start from the bench.
Really?
I've never played professionally,
don't lie to me.
Lu Yue is right.
Back in the days
when Cheng started to play professionally,
he was also a substitute.
It only took him a year
to make the player shiver
and make him the substitute.
Correction.
He didn't make him shiver.
It's impossible
to make me shiver.
Shut up.
Who on earth was the person
that made the other shiver?
Hierophant.
Hierophant?
From TAT?
My brother and Hierophant
used to be each other's greatest substitute.
The strongest light and shadow
in OCK history.
Eat.
Are you trying to persuade me or what?
I'm trying to tell you
that gold will glitter no matter where it is.
Look at Cheng and Hierophant,
right?
They're both well respected.
One person rules one division.
All other attack players
will shiver
under the claws
of these two people.
The shadow that almost crumbled
after getting defeated by Tai for once,
I loathe her.
Don't be rude.
Repeat it.
Nope.
He won't repeat, then you do.
What?
Your brother is about to bully me.
First come first serve.
You came back too late,
and she's good at more shikigamis
than you.
Behave yourself.
Why are you standing by her?
None of your business.
Did you hear it? Did you?
First come first serve.
I'm good at more shikigamis
than you.
You should behave, too.
The two of you
have never participated
in an official competition before.
To play safe,
isn't it normal to have a substitute?
If you guys want to be part of the lineups,
then get it with your skills.
Good. Great.
I really respect
Cheng's suggestion this time.
Anyway,
this is the fairest treatment
I've seen.
Really.
(One, two, three, four.)
(Five, six, seven, eight.)
(Two, two, three, four.)
(Three, two, three, four.)
(Five, six, seven, eight.)
(Four, two, three, four.)
(Five, two...)
Cheng.
As the captain,
you have to set a good example.
(Six, seven...)
I got 20/20 vision.
I can even see what Korean drama
the other team is watching
and which the episode is from here.
With such excellent eyesight,
do I still need to do this?
(Six, seven, eight.)
(Seven, two, three, four.)
ZGDX really got renovated
while I was gone.
A family should do things together.
This is the new computer the club sent you?
Correct.
I don't ever have to fight
for a seat with that fool again.
What era is this now?
How are you guys still doing eye exercises?
I bought you guys eye protection lamps.
You guys won't have to
worry about eyes stinging,
no matter how long you have to stare at
the computer in the future.
Everyone has got one.
You have to use it!
That's thoughtful of you.
Of course.
Fool.
Come here!
Stupid.
Get over here.
(Triple Kill)
(Assist)
(Ultra Kill)
(Defeat)
(Shorty, how long will you keep training?)
(I'll keep training as long as)
(you do.)
(Why are you copying me?)
Jinyang, how are you with Ai Jia?
Looks like you guys got back together.
I placed him
on the list of intern boyfriends.
We'll see how it goes.
You guys have been together for six years,
and he's been on your intern list six times.
He was never fired.
I'll shut up.
(The headshots and schedules
are out for the new season playoff.)
(Take a look.)
What is it?
Headshots for the National League.
National League?
The National League that
you're going to host.
Jinyang,
you should at least
learn a little bit about your part-time job.
I just need to show up looking pretty.
I don't need to know this.
Your biggest fan has decided to host
to show her support for you.
What are you sighing for?
Because of Lu Yue,
our team hasn't yet decide in the lineups.
It has to be you!
My bestie is so awesome!
Not necessarily.
Cheng said he needs to be fair.
I'm quite worried
how to get him
to lean toward me.
Don't worry.
Girls must have confidence in themselves.
Let me take you to choose your battle suit.
Battle suit?
What's that?
Our team just finished
choosing the team uniform.
It's different.
This is not the same kind of battle suit.
This.
This is what you mean?
Go try it on.
A perfect woman
will need to respond to all emergencies
with her sexy look.
I'm going to take headshots,
not wedding photos.
Well said.
Tomorrow marks the first time of
you and Cheng taking a photo together.
I hope that the next time
I see you guys together in a photo,
it would be one on a marriage certificate
taken at the Civil Affairs Bureau.
You're thinking way too much.
Best wishes to you.
My silly bestie captured the heart of
the God of E-sports.
If that day comes,
I can brag about it for a lifetime.
How did I have a friend like you?
This black clothes being too transparent,
how can I wear it inside?
Am I going to play or not?
Blurry beauty, you get it?
Then try this on.
Get cracking.
Go.
This is so cute.
Even underage girls
don't dress like that anymore.
I like it.
Okay then.
Go try both of these on.
Is it necessary?
Alright.
Since the starting players
haven't been decided yet,
there's no use in worrying about it now.
Anyway, you have to get your photos
taken tomorrow,
show your Captain
with your spirit
that you're his best partner.
When the CP photo of you and Cheng
gets published,
the Internet opinion might be so enthusiastic
that the club will include you
in the lineups.
Alright, let's go!
Please, please.
Go, go, go.
Why do you look like you're lying on
the chopping board
when you should be enjoying the spa,
sighing from time to time?
Jinyang,
since Lu Yue is back,
am I no longer
part of the lineups
for this new season of playoffs?
You've said this
countless times today.
Keep yourself positive.
What's yours will be yours.
If not, you can't take it by force?
Okay?
Yeah.
Jinyang,
since Lu Yue is back,
won't I be able to play as a starting player?
Say something.
Jinyang,
am I not going to be…
You're not going to be the starting player.
I'm leaving.
Go.
Come on, Yao.
Bye!
Look what they did in the team fight.
I don't understand
what they are hesitating for.
Has to be a surprise attack.
Look at the economy on the other side.
Honey, honey.
Honey.
Why didn't you visit me?
You put on make-up
and styled your hair!
It's a pity that there is no camera
next to the water dispenser.
Lu Yue, you better be kind.
Why are you sitting in my chair
and eating my snacks?
Give it to me.
This stuff is fat.
I'm sharing your burden.
This is healthy food.
What do you know?
It's not fat.
Tong Yao,
can I have a moment?
What's up, Cheng?
You want some dried mango?
It's very sweet.
What is this?
How are you going to use the keyboard
with so many things on your nails?
Also, the long eyelashes.
Won't it cover your sight?
Are you trying to suffocate your teammates
with your strong perfume
and lose the game?
If you want to be the starting player,
focus on your training.
Don't do anything meaningless.
I caught a backroom deal at the scene.
Delete it.
Nope.
If you dare to tell mom again,
I won't be nice to you.
Cheng, you've changed!
Yao,
I forgot to tell you.
Guess who I bumped into
the day before yesterday?
A ghost?
Hell no.
I bumped into my roommate.
She is with our class monitor now.
(Such a heartless
and thick-skinned girl like her)
was blushing and all shy
in front of our class monitor.
I could see her heart
pumping like crazy.
Her heart pumping like crazy?
Sounds like the reaction of
seeing a ghost to me.
Don't interrupt me.
Tong Yao.
What?
Did Biscuit eat your manicure and eyelashes
that we did together?
Cheng didn't like it.
Yao,
I've realized that
Cheng is the only one
who can have a say over you now.
How did we get to Cheng again?
You literally crumbled
at the bar last time.
Cheng took you away,
and you went back to normal the second day.
Tell me,
did he do something to you?
Be honest with me.
Do you feel joy, a speedy heart rate,
and blood rushing to your face
whenever you think of Cheng?
(Don't come back too late.)
You have three seconds.
Answer quickly.
If you don't answer,
then I'll take it as a yes.
Have you fallen for Cheng?
I…
Have you?
Tell me.
Yao.
You are in love.
Biscuit.
Why didn't you knock on the door?
Why didn't you lock the door?
I forgot to.
I was too lazy.
I thought you rolled off the bed.
(Oh my goodness, Cheng,)
(you guys are really together!)
Everyone went to bed quite early today?
We have to take promotional photos soon,
so I had everyone go to bed early.
You're really a team bully.
Cheng,
(why are you coming out from here?)
She just rolled off the bed,
I went to give a hand,
and see a joke by the way.
Listen,
she fell off again.
Well, are you going to go in
and give her another hand?
Forget it.
People must learn to grow on their own.
(Tong Yao)
(Mocked me again.)
(I heard it.)
(I won't bring you to victory tomorrow.)
(Remember to take your medication
before going to bed.)
(You have to treat your crazy disease
as soon as possible.)
(The sun came out from the west?)
(Night owl old man)
(actually woke up early
in the morning to read?)
Come on.
(Doce Cuentos Peregrinos)
(What a profound book title.)
(I can't understand it.)
Yao,
you are in love.
Go away.
Cheng, you're up so early.
The mid-season game today includes CK,
so I got up early to take a look.
Did it win?
Smashed Red Arrow and Obsidian,
and got destroyed by Alpha, as always.
Feel a joy, a speedy heart rate,
- and blood rushing to your face...
- Shut up.
What?
Nothing.
What are you doing?
There is a hair on your hair.
Biscuit's hair.
I'm training my waist and abdomen today.
Yao, want to go work out?
- Go go.
- Let's go.
- Let's go, gym time.
- Go.
- Let's go.
Healthy nuts,
healthy life.
Not bad.
Muscle.
You're not the starting player
for the National League,
why are you training so hard?
You are the starting player either,
and why are you so serious?
It's already a done deal.
Don't make your assumption
sound like a fact.
You can't afford to scare me to death.
I'll definitely be the starting player.
You will definitely not be.
Why are you copying me?
When did I copy you?
Childish.
Cat.
What is it?
Have you ever seen a dummy this close up?
Dummy?
Where?
There.
What happened to them?
And you.
What's that smell?
Dummy.
You can't be serious.
We got our new team uniforms.
The team uniforms are here. Take a look.
How is it?
This is better.
Weren't you the one who said
black will show shapes and look better?
Just right.
This is call make the best of what you got,
okay?
Didn't you say you are afraid of getting fat?
That's such a lie.
You're not even half the size of my uniform.
When a girl says they're fat,
can you believe her?
It's not a question of being fat or skinny.
It's just that everything she wears
looks like children's garments.
What did you say?
Can you be polite?
Who wears children's garments?
(A perfect woman)
(will need to respond to all emergencies)
(with her sexy look.)
♪Whose reasoning and expectations♪
♪Don't seem to be my inner monologue♪
♪To be myself or to run away♪
♪Should I just sway with the wind?♪
♪You're the one
who came through the sea of stars♪
♪Those corners open unexpectedly♪
♪It seems someone will really understand♪
♪My helplessness♪
♪The loneliness that
comes with the gradual leave♪
♪I'm beginning to believe♪
♪The existence of a tacit understanding♪
♪That fate can be changed♪
♪Because persistence♪
♪Has never been pale♪
♪The successes and failures
we have gone through♪
♪The crowd of people cheering tomorrow♪
♪Your look fuels my passion♪
♪Welcome the sunshine♪
♪Let's welcome the sunshine♪
♪Do you still remember♪
♪That I watched the shooting stars
pass by with you♪
♪How many times I seem to have heard♪
♪The wish I made that night♪
♪We all made a promise♪
♪Youth is about no regrets♪
♪If I have a dream in my heart♪
♪I'll follow the light♪
♪The moment we ignite with passion♪
♪Will light up the night♪
♪How foolish the stubbornness
that no one understands♪
♪How strong the desire to return to glory♪
♪Remember that moment at the top♪
♪Let's welcome the sunshine together♪