I'm not good at Tamamo-no-Mae at all.
I don't deserve to be the No.1 Tamamo-no-Mae
on the Chinese server.
Won't she be devastated from now on
and not dare to play ever again, will she?
Rui, I'm going out for a while.
It's already eleven o'clock.
Why isn't Tong Yao back?
Could the silly girl have gone to
jump into the sea?
Hello, bring me another glass
of iced black tea.
Hell no.
That's Long Island Iced Tea.
But I saw on the internet
the newcomer Smiling you recruited
was beaten up by Tai.
I wasn't beaten up.
I'm actually really good.
Am I going to be a substitute's substitute?
You can't keep me on the bench.
I just lost one game.
I don't want to guard the water dispenser.
(Alcohol may take your mind off
your sorrows for a while.)
(But we won't.)
They can say what they want to say.
We'll just focus on our own thing.
Jian Yang.
You don't know me at all.
You don't even know what I care about.
What I care about
is never what those people
on the Internet say.
I don't like to drag my teammates down.
As her teammates,
we must understand her at a moment like this.
To me, Tamamo-no-Mae is...
Like a sort of faith.
How about building a new faith
in regard to the determination to win?
(Smiling.)
(It's time to get up and face it.)
=Falling in Your Smile=
=Episode 07=
Who are you, Miss?
Good morning, Rui.
Good morning.
Your performance last night was great.
Cheng, why don't you let me
be the starting player?
I don't want to
guard the water dispenser over there.
I'll sing a song for you.
Could you let me be the starting player?
Flying Bugs... Flying Bugs...
Who are you thinking of?
How is it? Is it any good?
How's my singing?
Cheng, I want to be the starting player.
I'll sing one more song.
Will you let me be the starting player?
Ready, go.
The stars in the sky are flying.
The flowers on the ground are wilting.
Flying Bugs... Flying Bugs...
Who are you thinking of?
Let me be the starting player.
Let go of me. Let go of me.
Don't move.
Cheng.
Are you going to hurt me
just so your younger brother
can be the starting player?
No, I'm the No.1 player of Tamamo-no-Mae
on the Chinese server.
You can't do this to me.
Cheng, your little girlfriend
is quite a fighter.
Shut up.
Open her mouth.
Come on, open your mouth.
Come on, take the medicine.
Don't bite my hand.
Drink some water.
Come on, drink some water.
Drink it.
(Who do you want, Lv or me?)
(You're not really abandoning me,
are you? Boo-hoo...)
(I have a dream
and I want to be a professional.)
(I want to win the world championship.)
Wukong.
Where is my yogurt?
There were five or six cans last night
before I went to bed.
What are you doing?
What the hell are you doing?
Thinking about my life.
Thinking about your life?
Starting from what moment?
Let me guess.
From
one second before you were born,
or about 15 hours ago
when you had your first glass of
Long Island Iced Tea?
I guess it's the latter.
Because what happened at that time
is complicated enough
to make you think for a long time.
Captain.
Did I do a lot of improper things last night?
Improper?
No, how come?
Which one do you mean exactly?
You mean
When you were so scared that
you thought he was a ghost
when seeing my brother,
or when you cried that
you were too good
to be a substitute,
otherwise, you would lose the whole world.
That's when you even started to
sing "Flying Bugs".
By the way,
I should advise you.
You really shouldn't sing anymore.
Because you really turned
a children's song into a ghost's song.
You also forced your teammates to accept
the tissues after blowing your nose
one by one,
saying they were farewell gifts.
No refusal was accepted.
Otherwise, you'd hug him and then cry.
You even licked your cat's hair in the end,
and kept your cat's ear in your mouth.
Several people couldn't even pull you off.
You even bit people in the end.
To be frank,
I woke up early
to go get a rabies vaccination.
So, did you take your medicine?
What kind of medicine?
A sobriety pill.
It's put on your doorstep.
How can your illness get better
without medication?
Stop it. Stop it.
I know I'm wrong.
Who knew that drink had alcohol in it?
It's called Long Island Iced Tea.
Because there's no sweetheart
in sweetheart pastry.
There's no squirrel
in Squirrel Mandarin Fish.
There is no Lei Feng in the Leifeng Tower.
So of course,
Long Island Iced Tea is not tea.
Bumpkin.
And
what do you think
you're doing downstairs in your pajamas?
What do you want to do with this mask?
You want to scare us to death so that
you can kill us and silence us for good?
Can I not take off the mask?
Why are you wearing this?
It's embarrassing.
You mean you know what's embarrassing?
That's not what you said
when you asked us to guard your dirty tissues
after blowing your nose yesterday.
I won't listen, I won't listen.
Get up and change your clothes.
They're about to wake up.
(Switch to voice chat)
(Amao's Mom)
Hey, Yao, what's up?
Looking for me?
Are you sober?
What exactly happened at the bar yesterday?
I have no idea.
Nothing else matters.
You just need to remember
it was Cheng
who carried you away
in front of your ex-boyfriend.
Ex-boyfriend?
Jian Yang was there too?
I blame the idiot Ai Jia.
He just had to call him to come there.
Honey.
Who are you calling an idiot?
Who's there?
(Tong Yao)
(Something's going on?)
(Message: Yao, are you awake?)
(Let's get back together, Yao.)
(Yao, have you returned to the base?)
(Where are you?)
(You'll get a headache
in the morning after drinking.)
(Remember to drink some hot water.)
Take this.
No.
I asked you to take it.
Just take it.
You look like a big idiot.
Shut up.
There are too many people
in the supermarket today.
It's crowding me to death.
I think it's all right.
- Come on
- It's okay.
Look, Chubby. They all taste good.
What food?
Tong Yao.
You're up so early
to play double-queues with Cheng?
How's your record coming along?
Hello, Chubby.
How come it's you?
Lu Yue, why are you back?
I'm back.
What's wrong?
What?
I just got suspended.
It's not like I retired.
Why are you all so surprised?
Cheng.
Where are Rui and Ming?
Do they know?
We ran into each other last night.
I'm going to look for Ming.
Smiling.
What's your new trick?
She's ashamed to face people.
Why are you still here?
Because the team needs me.
No.
Yes.
- Yes.
- No.
This is my spot.
Is it?
Call it by name then,
and see if it makes any reaction.
You get up.
No.
- You get up.
- No.
Oh my God, Cat.
Why are you licking my cat's ears?
Both of us are about to
reach 24-year-old.
Why are you still acting like retards?
She's more of a retard, isn't she?
Made some kind of stupid lie for a chair.
Yet somehow you bought it.
You're even dumber.
Anyway, it's my chair now.
Whatever you say.
Biscuit.
When did I lick your ears?
What's going on?
Why are you eating with a chair?
Afraid I'll steal yours?
This is the chair that belongs to
the starting midsolo.
You're the worst midsolo
in the history of my team.
But still better than you as a substitute.
Not bad.
The food has been upgraded
while I was away.
What are you doing?
You're not eating?
No.
I'll eat over there.
How long are you going to be crazy for?
When will you leave?
Until I'm too old to hold a mouse.
Until he is too old to hold a mouse,
and doesn't compete with me
to be the starting midsolo.
Save it for
when you can beat Tai.
That's enough.
You've already lost your face.
Wearing a mask won't save your dignity.
Eat.
K, Chubby.
Why are you eating there?
You're fighting over the chair too?
What's wrong?
I don't want to eat here either.
It's not suitable for me to stay here.
No way.
I'm here to avenge ZGDX.
I was thinking about
why I couldn't fall asleep.
Some people not only take my place,
but also make a mess of my account.
Brat.
Cheng, why don't you
take care of her cursing?
Didn't you go to bed already?
Why are you down here again?
There are always unruly people
who want to occupy my spot.
How can I sleep in peace?
Look who's here?
Tai?
Will you go for it?
Does he know who's in the fight?
He has chosen Tamamo-no-Mae.
Why do you still choose Higanbana?
I'm playing this time.
Why panic?
Do you think
he can still show off this time?
You and your brother
really have the same character.
Condescending and arrogant.
Watch your language.
Anyway, whether
you'll win or lose this time,
I guess the image of me as a retard
has been ingrained
in Tai's mind.
Sooner or later,
I'll grind him beneath my heel,
and defeat him.
Why do you care what he thinks?
Are you out of your mind?
Keep tabbing.
What's wrong with you?
What's the point?
You can't kill it and you'll also miss
the money from the soldiers.
Are you stupid?
Want to run?
Where to?
Good job.
You're not bad.
Don't hit me.
Cheng, take her way.
I missed a soldier.
Intrigued me again?
Tai is not so smart either.
Trying to trap me twice in the same way?
No.
I'm the one who's not smart.
Yes.
He can only fool you.
He even came to my place to get killed.
He looks like he has helpers.
Trying to set me up?
No way, my friend.
I also have my teammates.
Why do you let others kill him?
But to be honest,
if it were me,
I would have fought with them.
I'm a wimp.
It's safer to be a wimp.
Yes.
Good for you.
Nice.
I have to admit,
you're quite something.
Do you know what it means
to come prepared?
I've studied all of
Tai's videos of playing games before.
I also played
as a substitute for Ming before.
Whenever he needed a defensive midsolo,
I'd be on the bench.
That's why last season's results
were quite a success.
What's the point?
What's the point of
having the best results of finalist season?
We still didn't even go to the finals
because of someone...
And finally gave
the trophy to the opponent.
Think about it.
Who actually led to
Ming's severe hand injury?
I don't know what you think.
I still stick to my opinion.
If this guy should be a substitute,
that's fine.
That's the choice of the club.
But I personally
don't accept this kind of teammate.
You guys go on. I'll go check it out.
It's been so long since this happened.
Why mention it?
Ming himself didn't say anything.
Do you think everyone is like you,
being all okay
only if they don't mention about it?
Why are you being mean to me?
He's right.
It's my fault.
Continue your gaming.
(Do you know what it means
to come prepared?)
(I've studied)
(all of Tai's videos of
playing games before.)
(I also played as a substitute
for Ming before.)
(Whenever he needed
a defensive midsolo,)
(I'd be on the bench.)
(Jinyang, I lost to a substitute.)
(I saw he was quite good at
playing midsolo.)
(Better than me.)
(What should I do?)
(I feel like I can't hold
my position as the starting player.)
(I loathe myself. I'm not happy.)
(I'm emotional.)
(I feel vulnerable again.)
We still didn't even go to the finals,
because of someone,
and finally gave
the trophy to the opponent.
(ZGDX withdrew the game)
(ZGDX won this year's championship)
(during the spring finals of
the Onmyoji Arena Pro League.)
(And the team fought all the way,)
(as if they were invincible,)
(in the National League.)
(Just when everyone thought ZGDX)
(was in closed training,)
(preparing for the national finals of)
(the Onmyoji Arena Pro League,)
(ZGDX officially announced
some shocking news.)
(ZGDX)
(withdrew from the national finals of)
(the Onmyoji Arena Pro League.)
(The Internet was full of curses
at that time.)
(Some said that ZGDX
was withdrawn from investments,)
(and faced disbandment.)
(Some said that there was a problem
among the members.)
(They couldn't play at all.)
(Some even said
they just couldn't handle the pressure)
(and gave up.)
(All in all, there were a lot of stories.)
(But there was no accurate answer
in the end.)
(A year ago, in the finals,)
(ZGDX was not
on the list of participants.)
Think about it.
Who actually led to
Ming's severe hand injury?
(Does Lu Yue have something to do with)
(these so-called stories that)
(even Ming was involved in?)
(Lu Yue Withdrew the Game)
(Is no one discussing that did Smiling)
(just take revenge on Tai?)
(The general channel for the South Korean server
is now heatedly discussing about it.)
(Is it possible that Lv played for her?)
(Lu Yue has ruined Ming.)
(Don't come out)
(to sabotage
the Chinese e-sports industry, okay?)
(Speaking of the starting player,)
(I still support Smiling.)
That's weird.
How do they know Lu Yue is back?
I don't know how Ming and Rui
think about it.
I really didn't intentionally provoke it.
What was his attitude like today?
You saw it, right?
We can't just let this event pass.
Someone has to say something, right?
I thought after all this time,
he could change.
But
he just casually
came back
as if nothing had happened.
And he even had the nerve to say that
he once was the substitute of Ming.
Look at this.
(Been here!)
He even announced it to the whole world,
as if nothing had happened.
Maybe he thought it had faded away
after a year.
But Ming's hand...
Are you pretending to be ghosts here,
not sleeping at midnight?
Why aren't you asleep?
I can't sleep.
Why? You ate too much?
Because of Lu Yue, right?
You all saw the game today.
Lu Yue was indeed more stable
than me in playing the game.
Maybe it'll make more sense
if he is the starting midsolo.
Don't worry.
Lu Yue will definitely
not be the starting player.
Not all mistakes
can be covered up by time.
What do you mean?
All right, Tong Yao.
Don't think too much.
Go to bed right after
you've finished drinking.
I'm too sleepy.
I'm going to leave now.
Good night.
(Jinyang)
Hello?
(You're still sleeping, Yao?)
(Oh my god, something big
is going on in your team.)
(Watch the video I sent you.)
(Our Ming's hand.)
(Oh my God, I'm going to cry.)
(This video was released by Smiling, right?)
(She looks like a sweetheart, normally.)
(But she's got a lot of evil intentions
behind her back.)
(Maybe she released this video)
(because she's afraid that Lu Yue)
(will steal her chance to be
the starting player in the National League.)
(Good point.)
(What a cunning bitch.)
Okay, don't worry.
Don't worry, we'll take care of it properly.
Yes, we as the authority...
It absolutely has no impact
on the daily operation of the team.
There is absolutely no problem
among our players.
Don't worry, we've prepared
a letter from the lawyer.
We still need to ask you
to discuss it with the headquarters.
Please talk about it. Don't give up.
I'll treat you someday
to show my gratitude, Mr. Xu.
What's the situation?
I'll give you a few more tickets
for the next competition.
Focus on your own business.
This is it for now.
- Okay
- Please, please.
All right.
Cheng, where's Chubby?
He went to the bathroom.
He said he'd be right down.
Hello, Tong Yao.
I'm the one running the official account.
The official account is now overwhelmingly
judged by people.
There're a lot of people complaining about
Lv and asking for the truth.
And Miss Tong.
The fact that you gave a thumbs-up
to a blog by mistake
is now also on the top
of the comment section.
Look at it.
The following are all malicious comments.
Laugh your ass off.
We can't just remain silent
and not reply this time.
We have to think of a solution
as soon as possible.
Lu Yue, stop looking through it.
There are barely
even a few positive comments.
Don't read it.
Rui, I'm going to solve the problems
of the official account.
Hello?
You regret it, right?
I told you back then.
Professional players
are also half public figures,
who should behave
differently from in school.
Keep a low profile,
in case you harm others as well as yourself.
First of all,
it's definitely targeted at Lu Yue.
He just returned to the club
after his suspension
before someone released the video.
It's obviously
to prevent him from returning
by means of public opinion.
Only our own people in the team have
this video.
To be honest,
why would the news
be so well sealed off back then?
Because there were absolutely
no more than 20 people
who saw this video,
or had access to this video
plus the staff of the KTV and the police.
The security guards of
the KTV and the police,
were a group of middle-aged people
in their 30s and 40s.
In their opinion,
it had nothing to do with e-sports.
It was just a group of young people
fighting and brawling.
The rest of the people who know about this
are members of our club as well as JK.
People of JK
definitely wouldn't dare
have released the video.
Because in terms of
public opinion suppression,
releasing this video
wouldn't benefit them at all.
It was also the result of our joint decision
to suppress it at that time.
They acted even more eager
to do this than we did.
Why?
Didn't Lu Yue start it?
But they fought back.
In self-defense?
That's not how self-defense works.
They were trying to subdue Lu Yue,
holding him down
and trying to grab the weapon he was holding.
That is called self-defense.
Then they beat him up.
That is called a mob fight.
But in my opinion,
it's also called deserving it.
All right, all right.
Anyway, this must have been
done by someone among us.
I don't know who it was.
But on behalf of the club,
I hope you can step up
to solve this properly.
There are so many rumors out there.
Everyone is on the edge of the storm.
If we don't unite internally at this time,
there will really be a big problem.
I posted the video.
Chubby?
I'm sorry, Tong Yao.
I didn't think you would get involved.
I only did this for Lu Yue.
With the same words being said,
that's fine
if he wants to be a substitute.
That's the club's choice.
But I personally
don't accept such a teammate.
Chubby, stop it.
You would agree to let
such a person return to the team?
I can't.
I won't accept it either.
What are you talking about?
He's to blame for Ming's retirement.
He has to give us all an explanation.
He's not to blame for my retirement.
Ming.
You think you can cover up all his mistakes
by shielding him like this?
Why did you have the fight?
Why did you get Ming involved in?
Why did you drag the whole team down?
You thought you looked cool
when you hit people with a bottle, right?
I was also very cranky and often fought
when I was in school.
But I don't do that anymore.
Why?
Because I knew I was a professional.
Fighting
would not only
get me punished and criticized,
but also affect my teammates, the club,
and even the entire industry of e-sports.
From a small perspective,
Ming's entire career
was ruined
because of your hit.
We couldn't go to the national finals
because of this shit too.
The whole team's efforts
for a whole year were in vain.
To put it in a big perspective,
Do you know what onlookers
say about e-sports industry?
They say we are internet addicts.
We don't do our jobs properly.
What's the point of just playing games?
I hear that every year.
I'm tired of hearing it,
but I still can't raise my head.
Because no matter how hard I try
to explain to others,
saying we're not like that,
we're not just punks
who only know how to play games,
then somehow there will be
stupid teammates like you who instead
prove millions of those people right
with your actions.
That we are what they say,
a bunch of losers.
(Amao's Mom)
(Oh my God.)
(The video was released by Chubby.)
(Chubby? That Chubby?)
Honey.
I've made you
a delicious breakfast with love.
Come on, have a glass of soy milk.
(Chubby is arguing with Lu Yue.)
(What should I do?)
(I feel so embarrassed.)
(Who am I, where am I and what am I doing?)
(The video was really released by Chubby?)
(Being in the same team,
why slaughter each other so frightfully?)
Honey.
You are talking about
the online video of the fight, right?
I was there at the time.
Who is your honey?
Mind your words.
You are still under review.
Don't make me deduct your points.
Ai Jia, are you crazy?
How dare you touch my lipstick?
Honey, don't be angry.
I'll show you something.
You see?
Light wave of love, BiuBiuBiu.
Screw you.
This is the love lipstick
I rushed to purchase.
Don't make me deduct your points.
Don't deduct my points.
How about this?
Do you want to know the truth of the event?
You know the truth?
Of course, I do.
The truth is often more than meets the eye.
Do you want to hear about it?
Just tell me if you want.
If not, get out.
Wait.
The person who caused such an accident
and brought us so much trouble
just simply wandered outside for a year.
Now he can pretend that
nothing happened
and that he doesn't have to
take responsibility for anything?
Why?
Chubby, you made a mistake.
Lu Yue didn't fight
with others for no reason.
It's because what they said
was so harsh.
That's why he started the fight.
In this situation, we all might...
I wouldn't.
Obviously, it was Lu Yue's fault.
Why are you guys trying to
cover for him all the time?
No need to say anymore.
I was just a scumbag
who was impulsive
and dragged my teammates down.
But what's the difference
between your posting the video
and my fighting?
You also dragged our teammates down,
didn't you?
The difference between you and me is that
I have a sense of shame.
I take responsibility for my mistakes
while you
are always a coward who runs away.
What did you say?!
I'll say it as many times as I please!
- You're a coward.
- Shut up.
- Coward.
- I dare you to say that again.
- Sit down.
- Coward.
You're just a coward.
All right, Chubby, stop it.
Sit down. Sit down.
Let's go. Go out and calm down.
What are you doing?
Lu Yue, calm down.
Take a chill pill. Calm down.
Calm down.
Out of sight, out of mind.
As long as Lu Yue doesn't show up
in front of me,
I'll feel much better.
I know
it's boring to say all this
in such a serious way.
But that's what I think.
I know I'm a professional.
It's not like I'm doing anything shameful.
But I can't maintain any dignity.
Why?
I know that
the way I handled it was a bit extreme.
But I just can't understand
how could a person like Lu Yue
return to the team?
So,
what exactly happened a year ago?
Come on.
It's been a rough day for you today.
Relax yourselves.
- That's right.
- Come on.
I'm sorry about today.
It was pure luck.
I won by a narrow margin.
Come on, let's have a drink.
Come on, come on.
To Mr. Bao and Mr. Pan.
I'll drink to that first.
Cheers.
It's supposed to be an exhibition match.
Chessman is not here?
He's not feeling well today.
That's why he didn't come.
Come on, come on.
He's not feeling well?
I thought he looked quite well
in the middle of the game just now.
He's clearly not showing respect to A.
No, no.
How come?
A, let me make a toast to you.
He's really not feeling well today.
Well.
Let's just say we had
a narrow victory today, okay?
Sorry.
A narrow victory?
You call two-love a narrow victory?
You're just looking down on us.
No, I'm not.
I...
Come on.
It was really pure luck today.
I'm drinking it for my brother.
I'll show you respect
To you all.
Yes, this is from Lu Yue.
This can be seen as being from Lu Yue.
Come on, I'll make a toast myself.
Come on, let's have a toast.
Come on, I'll fill it for you.
Come on, come on.
Come on.
Lu Yue. Lu Yue.
Good.
Good for you.
It's okay, it's okay.
You're the man.
Friendship comes first,
competition comes second, right?
Yes. Come on.
Are you okay?
Come on.
I'll make a toast to you all. Here.
I'll make a toast to you all.
- Come on
- Let's drink together.
- Let's drink.
Thank you for your hard work.
We've all worked hard today.
Good for us.
Come on, drink up.
Come on, let's have a drink.
Let's drink together. Come on.
Drink it.
Later,
Lu Yue probably heard
A making fun of our team in the toilet.
What the hell is ZGDX?
The players look so arrogant.
That's right.
Especially the one called Lu Yue,
what's he so arrogant about?
He's the one who got into the team
because of Lu Sicheng, right?
He is Lu Sicheng's brother.
Lu's family is too aggressive.
It's okay to be
a little bit proud in the game.
His brother didn't even
come to the party tonight.
And he still dared to shout at us.
They didn't show you any respect, A.
A, you must not let them off the hook.
We have to deal them a little something.
He's just like his brother,
unbeknownst to praise.
How dare he not show respect to our A?
What the hell.
Lu Yue.
- A.
Ming.
Stop it!
I'm calling the police.
- Let's go, A.
- Ming.
Go.
- Go.
- Just go.
Let's go.
It really has come to this.
Ming is still justifying Lu Yue.
He said that A's words
were too harsh at the time.
Even a sober person
couldn't have accepted it,
not to mention the drunk Lu Yue.
He also said that
Lu Yue never wanted to hear others say
he got into the team because of Cheng.
But what I don't understand is
if Lu Yue didn't want to
hear it,
then prove it by his skills.
He joined the fight
after hearing some harsh words.
What was that?
Just because of some harsh words,
he got into the fight
and dragged Ming into it.
Why should Ming suffer
from the conflict between him and A?
Ming shouldn't retire so early.
What a price we've suffered
because of Lu Yue's impulsiveness?
Hasn't anyone thought about it?
(- Hey, Yao.)
- Jinyang.
(- I know).
- I'll call you back.
(Don't hang up, Yao!)
(Go watch Ai Jia's live streaming.)
(He's trying to help Lu Yue clarify online.)
Clarify?
Jinyang said we should go watch
the live streaming.
♪Whose reasoning and expectations♪
♪Don't seem to be my inner monologue♪
♪To be myself or to run away♪
♪Should I just sway with the wind?♪
♪You're the one
who came through the sea of stars♪
♪Those corners open unexpectedly♪
♪It seems someone will really understand♪
♪My helplessness♪
♪The loneliness that
comes with the gradual leave♪
♪I'm beginning to believe♪
♪The existence of a tacit understanding♪
♪That fate can be changed♪
♪Because persistence♪
♪Has never been pale♪
♪The successes and failures
we have gone through♪
♪The crowd of people cheering tomorrow♪
♪Your look fuels my passion♪
♪Welcome the sunshine♪
♪Let's welcome the sunshine♪
♪Do you still remember♪
♪That I watched the shooting stars
pass by with you♪
♪How many times I seem to have heard♪
♪The wish I made that night♪
♪We all made a promise♪
♪Youth is about no regrets♪
♪If I have a dream in my heart♪
♪I'll follow the light♪
♪The moment we ignite with passion♪
♪Will light up the night♪
♪How foolish the stubbornness
that no one understands♪
♪How strong the desire to return to glory♪
♪Remember that moment at the top♪
♪Let's welcome the sunshine together♪