[Song of Youth]
[Episode 1]
Waiter, bring me the wine.
Here you go.
Please come inside, Young Master.
Mao.
Lin.
I sincerely apologize for being late.
Take a seat, please.
Why isn't Young Master Zhang here yet?
Young Master Zhang's wife is not feeling well.
Young Master Zhang stays home
to look after his wife.
Help yourself.
Enjoy the music and tea.
It's time for the Shadow Play.
Shadow Play is here. That's great.
Come on.
De, take a seat here.
I gave up on wealth and name.
Bit goodbye to my parents
and start on the misery journey.
There are a lot of blaming and regrets
when all I did for the love I thought
is no longer there.
We will continue with Wang Bao Chuan,
"The 18 Years' Waiting
with Loneliness and Miserable."
That's the same old story
you have been telling.
This is the only song you know.
Keep repeating the same.
Treat us like a fool!
Such a boring story.
Can you do another one?
If you can't do it,
get us our refunds.
Refund. Refund. Refund.
Get off my way.
Get me my refund.
Refund. Refund. Refund.
Refund.
Get me my refund now.
Who says that he doesn't have
any more story to tell?
He has stories.
My name is Sun Yu Lou.
The incident happened when I was 18 years old.
That was the most happening year
of the Sun Family.
[Shunzhen Gate]
My eldest sister, Sun You Zhen
was appointed as Imperial Noble Consort
upon her arrival in the palace.
3000 beauties in the harem,
but she had all the love.
The emperor extended his love to the family.
My father, Sun Xun
was appointed as Senior Grand Secretary.
He was highly respected.
My mother, from the Shen Family is a Buddhism.
She is a vegetarian
and practices her prayer every day.
She is very kind,
but for some reason,
my father's concubines are very afraid of her.
When I was 18 years old,
a few of my father's wives passed away.
There was only Aunt Mei
who kept my mom company.
Speaking of Aunt Mei,
she seemed to be difficult to get along with,
but she was in awe of my mother.
If you don't feel like doing the prayer,
just head back.
Beauty is waiting for someone
behind the bead curtain.
She points her head down and frowns.
Tears could be seen on her face.
Not sure who's making her upset.
My eldest brother,
Sun Shi Jie is very knowledgeable
and talented.
My first young madam, Wu Yue Hong
is the only daughter of
General of Agile Cavalry, Wu Da.
My father and Wu Da are best friends
since they were young.
The Sun and Wu families agreed to
their children's marriage before they were born.
When their children are at their age
to get married,
they will get married.
However, my brother
doesn't like his wife that much.
Husband.
My dear.
How do I
look today?
You...
What are you dressed like that?
Husband,
you love Luo Shen
who could dance gracefully.
I could move as fast as a flying bird
and walk as a fairy.
Let me show you.
You are aping the beauty. That's absurd.
Where are you going, master?
Please don't go, Master.
Master.
Stop running, Master.
Shi Jian,
is there any difference between me
and the person in the painting?
I got it.
Let me tell you.
Lipstick's color of the person
in the painting is red.
Mine is Crimson.
Seems like the master is upset
about the lipstick color.
Shi Jian, bring the brush.
Get her color changes to Crimson.
What?
[Simbol of happiness]
Second young madam, Su Ying Xue
is the most talented woman in the Capital.
Not long after she gets married
to my second brother, Sun Jun Hao,
father gave his military power
to my second brother.
My second brother is very busy in the army
and seldom come home.
Both of them didn't spend time together.
My second young madam kills her time
with playing zither every day.
Everyone in the Sun Residence could hear it.
Oh, my.
Whose lipstick was that?
Lipstick?
Young madam got it wrong.
It's...
There are a lot of dishes with chilies today.
It must have been the chilies.
So, it was the chilies!
The chilies?
Yes.
I'm done.
It's the chilies.
A misunderstanding.
Was it the chilies?
You don't even get this red with my slap.
Prick up your ears.
If anyone is using this Capsicum red
in the Residence,
just tell me.
I will tear his face.
Yes, Third young madam.
I didn't do anything wrong.
Go. Get me a tub of chilies.
On your knees!
Aren't you love it?
That should be more than enough.
Oh, no.
I am dizzy
and nauseous.
Stop pretending!
After you finished these chilies,
you would be able to come clean.
Make... Make sense.
Eat it.
That makes sense. That makes sense.
Open your mouth.
That's not a big deal.
Third young madam, Xu Feng Qiao
is the current
secretary of the Grand Secretariat.
The daughter of Xu Yun He.
Xu Family has very few boys.
Third young madam raised as a boy,
who makes my lazy third brother
terrified as a mouse confronting a cat
whenever he saw her.
He could hardly hold his breath.
I can't do it anymore. It's too hot. Too hot.
Sun Jin Ge.
That's too hot.
How dare you drink the water!
It made it worse.
I've been diddled!
Stop right there!
I couldn't take it anymore.
Help.
Stop right there!
Come over.
I won't do it again, madam.
How dare you run?
Mom. Mom.
Come over.
You...
My father has four sons and four daughters.
Among all these siblings,
there is my second sister, Sun You De.
Third sister, Sun You Rong.
They are many years older than me.
They were married and away from home
when I was a kid.
Now,
my sister's faces are faded in my mind.
Try to catch me.
For a very long time,
my only companion is my fourth sister,
Xiao Xian is the youngest.
Ms. Sun.
I can't run anymore.
I have been home the whole day
and it's killing me.
Do you expect me
to hold still since we're out?
Ms. Sun, you...
If you dare to tell madam,
I will make myself fall
and you will take the blame.
What can you do to me?
Ms. Sun. Ms. Sun.
Fourth brother.
[The Finest Collection of Books]
[Yiqu Hall]
Fourth brother, father is looking for you.
Who is that?
Close the door now.
[Yiqu Hall]
Sit.
San Tai Zi, take my spear!
San Tai Zi is gone.
That's so funny!
What do you call this, Fourth brother?
This is Shadow Play.
It is very famous in the community now.
You know nothing, aren't you?
Who says that?
If father allows me to go out,
don't you think I wouldn't know
this is the Shadow Play?
Hey!
They're having a banquet in the Residence.
Father would like you to have a toast.
I am not interested
in this kind of socializing.
Everyone is good in their speech,
but you have no idea what's in their minds.
If you want me to bring myself down
to entertain them,
they don't worth it.
You're missing something then.
They're just acting. What would I miss?
I am making no loss.
But in the banquet today,
Lady Yu will be playing Pipa for father.
Third young madam said
that Lady Yu is the No.1 Pipa player
in the Capital.
If you missed it this time,
it'd be hard to have a second chance.
Pipa player!
Well, I already knew that fourth brother
wouldn't be there.
Let me inform father now.
Naughty girl.
Lady Yu,
the carriage of Sun Residence is here.
[Jingshu Hall]
[Wanfu Hall]
Master Li. Master Li.
This is amazing. This is amazing.
You are always welcome to the Residence.
Madam.
Recently,
did Third Young Master find any nice places?
That you had fun.
Father.
What took you so long? Take a seat.
[Amiability leads to harmony]
Wishing you good fortune and longevity.
Thank you.
Someone like Master Sun
who is a well-versed in career
and all children turned out to be outstanding,
make people envious.
I am wishing you a prosperous and good future.
That's the flattery you used
to survive in the field.
Thank you all for coming
to celebrate my birthday.
I couldn't thank you all for more.
Please help yourself with the food.
Please pardon me
if there is anything that I've missed.
Let's toast.
This glass of wine represents my appreciation.
Please enjoy the drink.
- We are wishing father,
- We are wishing master,
good fortune and longevity.
Please.
Come on.
Let's sit.
[Wanfu Hall]
Lady Yu is here.
Lady Yu. That's is Lady Yu.
I was told that fate is destined.
Well, when I look back I think that's true.
On my father's birthday that year,
I met that girl.
I was impressed at the first glance
and it changed my whole life.
You don't need a reason
to fall in love.
I saw her
and listened to her performance.
Then I know she is the one.
She is all I want.
Good.
That's good.
Check it out.
Lady Yu is a young lady.
Is that real?
I met Lady Yu once before.
If I calculate,
Lady Yu should be closed to 40 now.
Who are you?
Why are you pose as Lady Yu?
40!
Impersonate?
Yes.
Lady Yu is my master, Sir.
She doesn't feel well lately.
She worried Sir might be upset
if she is not able to perform,
which she sent me here.
I am here to celebrate Sir's birthday
on my master's behalf.
Lady Yu was the person
invited by Master Sun today.
If Lady Yu is not feeling well
and couldn't make it,
she should have informed us in advance.
How could she just send an apprentice
to fill it up?
That's right.
When everyone was listening
to the performance just now,
it was melodic and euphonious.
Everyone gave a round of applause
right after the first song.
Did anyone realize that she wasn't Lady Yu?
[Wanfu Hall]
But you are all being so mean
after seeing her face.
Please pardon my foolishness and if I may ask.
What would be literati looking for,
from the performance?
Is it the quality of the music
or the performer?
Of course, we pay attention to the music.
This...
My third brother made a very good point.
It's very difficult
to find a nice piece of music.
Since today is my father's birthday,
which is such a shame
if we didn't let go of stuff
that might not make it a good day.
In my opinion,
this lady shouldn't be punished
but to be rewarded instead.
Father.
Since you're the only one
who watched Lady Yu's performance,
do you think
this performer should be rewarded or punished?
Father, today is your birthday,
it should be ended in a good way.
Oh, my bad.
Lady Yu was here earlier to inform me that.
I must have forgotten.
This lady is Lady Yu's apprentice
who has learned well from her.
The performance just now was amazing
which she seems to do better than her master.
Listen up.
Master.
Grant the reward.
Yes.
Thank you, Master Sun.
[Intensity of beautiful garments]
Lady Yu,
may I ask if your apprentice is here?
Apprentice?
Yes. The lady who played Pipa
at Sun Residence yesterday.
She's the one you're looking for.
I'm wondering if you can introduce me to her?
Why are you looking for her?
I was impressed by her performance yesterday.
I wish that I could come today
to make acquaintance.
This... About this...
You didn't come at the right time, Sir.
She caught a cold last night
when she was home.
She is gone and we've buried her body.
My poor apprentice.
What are you doing? That's hurt!
My lady,
that girl knocked you out yesterday
and took all your credits in Sun Reside.
Why didn't you mention it?
Who doesn't know that me, Lady Yu
is the best Pipa player in the Capital?
She is just a fledgling player
who try to snatch my reputation.
Stop dreaming!
If she would like to address herself
as my apprentice,
I will let her be.
In the future, even if she is able
to make some small accomplishments,
she would still be under my name.
Good.
Please have the water, senior.
It's your turn, Xiao Yu.
Alright.
Be careful.
It's fine.
Senior, your headgear.
Alright.
Senior, come over quickly.
What's wrong? What's wrong?
Everyone comes over quickly.
What's wrong, Shao Chun?
Hurry up. Hurry up.
We are here. What's wrong?
Shao Chun, you are so good.
You can make this much money
by posing as Lady Yu.
Of course.
In the Bai Theatrical Troupe,
Shao Chun is the most skillful.
That's right.
This is our senior. Senior is the best.
We must keep it from the master.
Otherwise, we would be punished.
Shao Chun,
come with me.
Yes.
Master.
Master?
Do you still see me as your master?
You acted as bold as brass
with such little skill.
Do you have any idea
what kind of disaster
you could have made yesterday?
I just wanted to give it a try
to see if the skills I have learned
from you are useful.
The skills I teach you
are for you to perform on the stage.
I didn't ask to use them off stage.
But you would have known
that I will use them off stage eventually.
It's not the time yet.
So, when would it be?
When you can put up a nice play.
I earned my reward and a round of applause.
Aren't those good enough?
[Animitta]
If you think this little money you made
and a few people clapped for you
are considered as well done,
that wouldn't be anything more
I could teach you.
Go.
Master, this is not fair.
You would be lost
with being impatient
and rush for quick results.
Master.
[Animitta]
(You would be lost)
(with being impatient)
(and rush for quick results.)
(She caught a cold last night
when she was home.)
(She is gone and we've buried her body.)
(Ghost.)
(I love her)
(and it doesn't matter
if she is a human or ghost.)
Miss...
Are you the spirit of her, miss?
Who are you?
I saw your Pipa performance before
and I am impressed with your skills.
I was hoping to make acquaintance with you.
However, when I approached today,
I was told that you have passed away.
Passed away?
Miss,
are you alive or you are the ghost?
(Is he a fool?)
I'm a ghost.
Aren't you afraid of me?
I'm not afraid.
Do I have the pleasure
to have a drink with you?
That's good.
Please come with me to the Jaws of Death.
Miss.
Wait for me.
Where are you, miss?
Miss.
Miss. Miss.
Where are you, miss?
Miss.
Idiot.
I am home, granny.
You're home, Ms. Lin.
Lit the incense.
Why are you wet, Ms. Lin?
Nothing. I fell into the pond.
I couldn't be with you all the time
which you would have to
take good care of yourself, Ms. Lin.
How was your school today?
Imperial examination is right at the corner.
You're joining the troupe at day time
and studying at night.
You can't fall sick.
Let me get you some ginger soup
to keep you warm.
Granny,
I am not going
to the Bai Theatrical Troupe anymore.
Why?
I was kicked out by the master.
What should we do then?
What mistake that you have made?
Why you are being kicked out?
Let's beg Master Liu.
Ask for her forgiveness.
That's not needed,
I'm capable to succeed by myself.
Why are you being so stubborn, Ms. Lin?
The entire skills of this Liu Three Arts
are compiled into these Three Arts.
If you didn't complete the last art,
how would you be able to join the examination?
You are different from others. You are a girl.
If they found out,
it'd be a felony to get yourself killed.
It wouldn't happen, granny.
I have learned for so many years.
I would at least get some parts of it
which could help me to cover up.
If I didn't make it after all,
that's my destiny.
Ms. Lin, you...
Ms. Lin.
Jiang Cheng, appointed as
Wei Zhou's assistant commander at first.
He is persistent and brave.
He was introduced by Qian Ning
and summoned by Emperor Cheng Zong.
He was being promoted and his power expanded.
He abused his power and commanded the army.
Qian Ning was the second place
from the Imperial Examination.
His rank is the same
as secretary of the Grand Secretariat.
He is shrewd and good at planning.
He is calm and reserved,
who is very much trusted by the emperor.
Li Chong, Commander of the Imperial Guards,
straightforward but grumpy.
He joined the late emperor in war
when he was young with a splendid record.
Put into an important position by the emperor.
He is in control of the army
and everyone finds him intimidating.
By the grace of heaven's will,
His Majesty hereby proclaims,
[Memorial tablet of my late father,
Lin Dao Yuan]
Deputy Minister of Revenue, Lin Dao Yuan,
funds deduction of 50,000 kokus.
Corruption of 10,000 Fine silver.
To be flogged 80 times.
Confiscation of all properties.
Banishment of the entire family.
Let this be known
to the world.
Mother.
Shao Chun,
your father is no longer here.
I can't live with that.
I owe you this.
No.
No. No.
Madam.
- Mother.
- Madam.
Mother.
Your father was an honest
and upright officer in his entire life.
He has never been corrupting.
Why is this...
Mother.
I know that father is innocent.
It's a shame that you are a girl.
If you were a boy,
you would be able
to ask for justice for your father.
I'd be able to ask for justice for my father.
It's difficult.
Mother.
Madam.
I will ask for justice for my father.
Order to search. Please look carefully.
Go through with a fine-tooth comb.
Leave.
Take all people from the Lin Residence.
See how they would behave in the future.
Officer,
please spare us, let us go.
Help! I don't want to be banished.
Are you Lin Shao Chun,
the daughter of Lin Dao Yuan?
Take her.
Sir,
she is my daughter, Xiao Ya.
We are not from the Lin Residence,
we don't have the indenture.
Where is Lin Shao Chun?
There she is.
Mom.
Mom, I am not Ms. Lin.
Mom, I am not.
Mom.
Ms. Lin.
There is nothing much I could do.
We have to take care of ourselves.
I can't protect you anymore.
- Mom. Mom.
- Granny.
Ms. Lin. Ms. Lin, please. I am begging you.
Take her.
Ms. Lin, I am begging you.
Mom. Mom.
Mom.
(My daughter,)
(Lin Family treats us so well,)
(it's time for us to return their favor.)
(At least, you would be able to live.)
(There's hope as long as you're alive.)
Mom.
Ms. Lin,
take it while it's warm.
even since I replaced Xiao Ya with you,
I have taken you as my daughter.
After all these years,
Ms, Lin has suffered a lot
and you have got them through.
Now, we are just one step away,
we couldn't afford any mistake.
I know it well, granny.
Since you haven't completed the last art
of the Liu Three Arts,
what is your plan now?
I have told you many times.
You are already past the age to learn opera.
I couldn't take you in
even though you are on your knees.